toynewsi.com 2017-12-01

# ENewsi.com - Pop Culture Entertainment Iron Man, Batman, Star Trek, Transformers, Twilight, Harry Potter and more<%endif%>

## Entertainment News International Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Entertainment News International (ENI) websites. 

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any ENI website. On some pages, you can order advertising, make requests, and register / win competitions to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

* Name
* Email address
* Network IDs such as Twitter and AIM
* Profile info such as music and movie preferences

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when signing up for an account with ENI. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to support the sites. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

**Disclosing Information**

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Cookies**

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files "cookies" that hold information which allows a website to recognise your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired. You may also use your browser to remove any cookies placed by ENI servers.

**Third Party**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, email address or location) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we do not allow or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13. No part of our website is structured to allow anyone under 13.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your profile and accessing your control panel. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How You Can Remove Your Information**

You can contact us if you would like your account closed. Once we have verified your identity, we can remove all your personal details and IP on request.

**Modification of Policy**

This policy may be modified at any time at the sole discretion of the Provider. Upon modification of this policy, the User has two weeks (14 days) to terminate their account with the Provider or it will constitute acceptance of the modifications.

**How To Contact ENI**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact ENI by filling the [Contact Us Form](http://enewsi.com/submit-news.php).
